{"36160683282425": {"answer": 135, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "100 - -35 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "11523417116928": {"answer": -0.28, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "276 / -991 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "88869211378737": {"answer": -680, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-811 + 131 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "15781253207053": {"answer": 987, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "24 - -963 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "89233287385772": {"answer": 0.73, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "454 / 620 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "64944968602431": {"answer": 1048, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "749 + 299 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "90303209955503": {"answer": -734, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-10 - 724 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "82693632017071": {"answer": 9, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "150 - 141 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "22960741332405": {"answer": -1649, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-856 + -793 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "29184029145880": {"answer": -431, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-462 + 31 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "19946103463441": {"answer": -283338, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "583 * -486 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "82798037609828": {"answer": -396, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "204 + -600 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "82361230348297": {"answer": -222256, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "958 * -232 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "11078234204883": {"answer": -502, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-747 - -245 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "73012189215973": {"answer": -311, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-99 + -212 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "11666291202815": {"answer": 3486784401, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "3 ^ 20 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "78722909754879": {"answer": 56, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "308 - 252 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "48167730635328": {"answer": 2213314919066161, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "19 ^ 12 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "3633262539412": {"answer": 121, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "11 ^ 2 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "50272603730658": {"answer": -853, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "88 - 941 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "88842376133551": {"answer": 639108, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-738 * -866 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "49652221164805": {"answer": -111573, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "147 * -759 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "20607799102391": {"answer": 1242, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "628 - -614 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "97143678618143": {"answer": -0.91, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-557 / 613 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "16347971986636": {"answer": 517, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "116 - -401 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "90629584291845": {"answer": -312984, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-644 * 486 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "37417087228119": {"answer": 0.72, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-703 / -973 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "7322931477019": {"answer": -1592, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-936 - 656 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "68618706846965": {"answer": 0.72, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "644 / 894 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "71106141493486": {"answer": -339075, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-685 * 495 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "52679396957990": {"answer": 307, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "524 + -217 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "68412041208145": {"answer": -710, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-48 + -662 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "63844354579752": {"answer": -582, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-804 + 222 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "38378812545134": {"answer": 1728, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "12 ^ 3 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "35241020013547": {"answer": 1419, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "443 - -976 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "3162178570770": {"answer": 1253, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "544 + 709 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "66430416119735": {"answer": -276.33, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-829 / 3 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "14651876518951": {"answer": 166, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-31 + 197 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "96035581727974": {"answer": 150849, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-333 * -453 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "80856313107554": {"answer": 175616, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "896 * 196 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "32979120152036": {"answer": 416970, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "738 * 565 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "55102421745244": {"answer": 1, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "1 ^ 9 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "66953804139748": {"answer": -255, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "300 - 555 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "50030940549451": {"answer": -0.37, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "165 / -447 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "21194044130516": {"answer": 169200, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "470 * 360 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "98837559623301": {"answer": -1.19, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-623 / 523 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "48038063266253": {"answer": 655, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "716 + -61 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "11616212546905": {"answer": 606606, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-707 * -858 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "82125075814784": {"answer": 301, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "302 - 1 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "67801819105400": {"answer": -76950, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-675 * 114 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "79771424292136": {"answer": 0.77, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-150 / -196 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "266564564157": {"answer": -980, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-374 - 606 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "21045344478483": {"answer": 2401, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "7 ^ 4 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "723769974418": {"answer": 2.18, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "394 / 181 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "77331814258067": {"answer": -51624, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-478 * 108 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "50580370377098": {"answer": -66, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-236 - -170 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "54783906140581": {"answer": 203, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-613 + 816 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "77921785579049": {"answer": 3375, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "15 ^ 3 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "64457576293870": {"answer": 85, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "295 + -210 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "96808694345295": {"answer": -77, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-88 + 11 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "37197456436985": {"answer": 16777216, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "16 ^ 6 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "27360452496613": {"answer": -508, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-799 - -291 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "82049314036719": {"answer": 448, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-167 + 615 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "86881040957384": {"answer": -240, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-17 - 223 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "67012011289496": {"answer": -1.29, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "724 / -561 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "67675539213145": {"answer": 514, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-486 - -1000 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "372064012480": {"answer": -2.2, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "426 / -194 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "32690013493142": {"answer": 67445, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-205 * -329 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "88608160436226": {"answer": -1575, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-709 - 866 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "34416564458267": {"answer": 27, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "3 ^ 3 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "467392660807": {"answer": 1346, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "764 - -582 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "12646223705944": {"answer": 799006685782884121, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "19 ^ 14 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "85359612725107": {"answer": 1059, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "349 + 710 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "45196958789239": {"answer": 467, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "970 - 503 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "5550178861797": {"answer": 1000000000, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "10 ^ 9 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "32746191467059": {"answer": -1.26, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "866 / -690 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "4233402750755": {"answer": 0.45, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "356 / 784 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "94655583894346": {"answer": -851400, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "860 * -990 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "68545454406883": {"answer": 35831808, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "12 ^ 7 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "94660677455467": {"answer": 1, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "1 ^ 8 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "88313277606093": {"answer": -603, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-972 + 369 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "42355452426570": {"answer": -443, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "504 + -947 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "14640429796210": {"answer": 802256, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "988 * 812 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "29673228909314": {"answer": 0.26, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "224 / 865 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "93470988931495": {"answer": -511, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-86 - 425 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "10208389735743": {"answer": -464665, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-467 * 995 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "97622149797938": {"answer": -690, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-147 + -543 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "76689768803728": {"answer": 359, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "163 + 196 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "67237941677008": {"answer": 14, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "14 ^ 1 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "1429096903241": {"answer": -1.23, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-528 / 431 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "35922434869228": {"answer": 322687697779, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "19 ^ 9 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "45860485960602": {"answer": 0.37, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-311 / -847 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "55349710730739": {"answer": 2.7, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-345 / -128 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "57686472441997": {"answer": 10682, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-218 * -49 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "85538187571013": {"answer": 289254654976, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "14 ^ 10 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "66960435270163": {"answer": -1429, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-551 + -878 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "28115015338108": {"answer": -1126, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-823 - 303 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "35581540695671": {"answer": 1436, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "495 + 941 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "46075466888723": {"answer": -934, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "39 + -973 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "1062787177531": {"answer": -0.85, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-665 / 782 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "15914697804452": {"answer": 69, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "674 - 605 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "87155815095578": {"answer": -394875, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "675 * -585 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "40270215736605": {"answer": 0.87, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-686 / -789 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "37122101426848": {"answer": 30098, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "101 * 298 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "24455720631152": {"answer": 523, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "10 - -513 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "50636988254392": {"answer": -765, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-571 + -194 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "34754691111613": {"answer": 3375, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "15 ^ 3 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "15080645980611": {"answer": 1210, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "244 + 966 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "59149098555932": {"answer": 0.98, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-863 / -878 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "39220973774036": {"answer": -180, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-32 - 148 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "55386440356447": {"answer": 1179, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "739 - -440 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "33467075666168": {"answer": 1792160394037, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "13 ^ 11 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "77921688264130": {"answer": 1253, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "778 - -475 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "77147812115611": {"answer": 13, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "13 ^ 1 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "52541392362122": {"answer": 62310, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "134 * 465 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "31324510190928": {"answer": -0.2, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-166 / 840 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "46670115219849": {"answer": 3138428376721, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "11 ^ 12 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "75341294534122": {"answer": -4.15, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "933 / -225 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "92393320021313": {"answer": 230, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "272 - 42 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "6840640156832": {"answer": 1830, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "961 + 869 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "80592732244727": {"answer": 160402, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "634 * 253 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "40054806799540": {"answer": -741, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-197 + -544 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "59858569169911": {"answer": -0.88, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "716 / -814 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "32623620531420": {"answer": 1759, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "818 + 941 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "1350147909941": {"answer": -355286, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "802 * -443 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "21589621131185": {"answer": 144, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "12 ^ 2 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "46385374387139": {"answer": 1.37, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-799 / -583 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "41096329294924": {"answer": 1614, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "907 - -707 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "6229437111034": {"answer": 273, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "817 + -544 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "85990038768504": {"answer": 2176782336, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "6 ^ 12 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "18585042013944": {"answer": 721, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "996 - 275 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "86206799033955": {"answer": 283, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-147 + 430 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "76387536505259": {"answer": -0.01, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "3 / -445 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "13025224862166": {"answer": 486, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "254 + 232 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "64213227580685": {"answer": 54752, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "236 * 232 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "66929046751548": {"answer": -641, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "253 - 894 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "37757857112531": {"answer": 217562, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "362 * 601 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "27689240817996": {"answer": 0.62, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-408 / -654 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "57652288532885": {"answer": 489, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-48 + 537 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "41578618414824": {"answer": 150084, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "758 * 198 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "45344469601249": {"answer": 729, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "9 ^ 3 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "29575136151515": {"answer": 362797056, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "6 ^ 11 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "11589809087266": {"answer": 693, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-277 + 970 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "20767634508863": {"answer": 3200000, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "20 ^ 5 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "65147213166975": {"answer": 361, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "19 ^ 2 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "26676941504480": {"answer": 660, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-147 - -807 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "80809727132464": {"answer": 454510, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "602 * 755 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "22266568860649": {"answer": 655360000000000000000, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "20 ^ 16 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "2834534374089": {"answer": -0.04, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "44 / -997 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "58959336945545": {"answer": 56, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-773 + 829 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "93136020557362": {"answer": -4.9, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "867 / -177 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "57633114461077": {"answer": -246186, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "291 * -846 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "14029347875423": {"answer": -0.06, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-21 / 365 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "59717174441763": {"answer": 0.44, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "287 / 656 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "84103926524141": {"answer": -54, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-201 + 147 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "85151823300037": {"answer": -1657, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-751 + -906 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "47240983474655": {"answer": -575, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "327 - 902 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "66275972954967": {"answer": -23, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "934 - 957 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "87267870205698": {"answer": -623, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "198 + -821 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "66844621658127": {"answer": -18216, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-138 * 132 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "6515575393314": {"answer": -595, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-478 - 117 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "4648648495539": {"answer": -324, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-1000 + 676 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "98906530674593": {"answer": -0.76, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-552 / 728 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "36627500791792": {"answer": 1, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "1 ^ 5 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "1748881794330": {"answer": -0.09, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-61 / 693 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}, "5709048969998": {"answer": 2.56, "voters": [], "author": 845751152901750824, "solvers": [], "question": "-664 / -259 (Was automatically created by the bot)."}}